[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Is that the kind of fury that you have felt about issues over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It resonates a great deal and in many ways, some of them complicated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "I mean, are you proud to be an American right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I'm more proud to be an American than ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "And are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think largely people with simpler thoughts are more polite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What have been your thoughts in the last two or three years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I don't think that that matters as much as -- in the way that it's often talked about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you think America should become -- I mean, I'll be much more selfish about his foreign policy -- be more humanitarian in areas like Haiti, but leave the bombing to other people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "We don't have to tell it to ourselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Haiti"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq", "U.S."]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "RBR", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 106, "question": "I mean democracy and freedom, through the kind of uprising you saw in Tahrir Square, is massively more beneficial to America's interests than going into Iraq and behaving in the way that the allies did there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "If we had waited on Iraq, what we'd be seeing is Saddam Hussein being brought down by his people right now, without hundreds of thousands of dead Iraqis, children, U.S. soldiers, all the money that's been spent that could have been spent here to better this country, to straighten this country --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tahrir Square", "America", "Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rupert Murdoch"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Do you think that the power of these uprisings all over the world, in all different ways, means that those guys, their days are numbered, generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I think, frankly, Rupert Murdoch will be the teller of this, because I think the great despot are in the corporate world and that -- that the fact that a clown -- I mean Gadhafi, by any sober analysis, could have been three times as wealthy and a god to the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["HRO"], "LOCATION": ["Haiti"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What motivates you to go and literally get in there, live there and carry on working for this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", ",", "JJ", "EX", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, I think I would have to begin to answer that by saying because we live in a world doing the things that -- that my organization is doing in Haiti, J/P HRO, where we have dependencies and we have great appreciation for a lot of ways in which people contribute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Of all the Republican candidates, clearly, I suspect you're not going to vote for any of them, but if you had to, who is the one that you would prefer to see as the Republican nominee?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Of the Republican candidates, I would say Barack Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Who's the least threatening to your ideology?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "That we do not necessarily be the way that I would pick it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "So expectation was far too high, wasn't it, given the -- the state of the economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Yes, I'd like to see expectation get higher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, I do now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Hey, bud, what's your problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "No problem at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Have you crammed it all in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RBR", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Could you see yourself walking away from movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "You know, earlier, you said something about my being a multi-millionaire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "-- let me rephrase it, pre-divorce, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Yes, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Do you need -- do you need to make movies to -- to -- to live, to earn money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", ":", "IN", ":", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Look, I -- I still have a love affair with the movies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Do you go to the movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I go to the movies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", ":", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Regularly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Not regularly enough, because I'm always traveling around and -- and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What was the -- what was the best film you've seen recently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "ENN: \"Senna\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What to you is great acting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Well, let's see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna Magnani"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ":", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Which actresses would you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, look, and Meryl Streep -- Meryl Streep and Meryl Streep and -- and Anna Magnani and Meryl Streep and -- no, there's -- there's several actresses that I think are wonderful and, you know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Would Jack Nicholson creep in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Absolutely, Jack.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Nicholson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "If you could write your own tombstone, your own epitaph, what would it say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, let's see, I was -- first, I'd like to -- to erase some of my children's memories of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What about I'm still angry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes, aside from my kids, I don't really care if I'm even remembered, I don't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Are you going to take any action against the police?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yes, we may well do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Once you were both arrested, what happened then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "It was absolutely Kafkaesque.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Are you completely blameless here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, what happened was we were being pushed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arab Spring"]}, "docId": "111014pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "How big will it get, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Hopefully the equivalent of the Arab Spring, I mean, in the sense that -- again, it is a way of discounting people to say they are not organized.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]